evaphone.com 2012-11-20

# Free Call - Free International Calls & Free VoIP Service. Internet phone calls - Cheap VoIP, cheap online calls to phone over Internet telephony.

## Evaphone Privacy Policy

Evaphone respects the privacy of its customers and implement serious measures when it comes to protecting the privacy of its customers. This policy describes the personally identifiable information collected by Evaphone from its customers in a few words. Moreover, we are talking here about the steps needed to safeguard such information.

## Collection and Use of Information

Evaphone works by collecting and using personally identifiable information, these include name, email address, and credit card information. We use it for billing and provisioning of services, for solving problems associated with service, and for informing our customers on new products or services offered by Evaphone that will suit them best. There is a possibility that our company will also collect such information from prospective customers with the help of promotional campaigns which are conducted occasionally. There is a possibility that Evaphone will share such information with business partners in order to ensure the successful provisioning and operation of its services. Also we can use your data to smooth the progress of the marketing of Evaphone products and services. However, we never sell, trade, or disclose personally identifiable information to third parties for unrelated marketing purposes. Moreover, any customer willing not to receive information about new or different Evaphone products or services can simply refuse to receive such information.

Our company works with “cookies” when it comes to information gathering process. This is done to improve the quality of our web-site and make the quality of customer interaction with Evaphone better. We are talking about the ordering, provisioning, and billing procedures. Evaphone customers get a chance to choose to block the use of such “cookies”, though we would like to warn you, by doing so you make interaction with our company less efficient and this could limit the availability of certain web-site features.

## Security

Many technology and security features aimed at protecting the privacy of customer information on its network have been deployed by Evaphone. In addition, our company has implemented operational guidelines in order to defend customer privacy at all stages of work in the company. We will continue revising policies and implementing additional security features with the emergence of new technologies.

## Children’s Privacy Policy

Neither Evaphone products nor services can be purchased by children. We are not involved in the process of collecting customer identifiable information from minors under the age of eighteen. In addition, our company will not link web site to any third party that has or collects customer identifiable information from minors. If, by some reason, you think that a minor has disclosed personally identifiable information to Evaphone, please let us know and we will remove such information. 

## Evaphone Spam Policy

Using Evaphone for spamming purposes is strictly prohibited. If you use Evaphone facilities improperly, you will be deprived of your Evaphone privileges.

This agreement was last updated: 2012-07-23 09:00 a.m.
